I feel like people came around me heavy like and when I say heavy it's like they feel like I don't
know how she feeling you know like just kind of heavy and I'm like it's okay like I'm cool like
we can talk about her matter of fact let's look at some video like people like I don't want to do
should I play his music should I do this should I you know is it okay I'm like me and my kids
regularly will get in the bed and like look at old videos and pictures like that that's like
happy you don't have to be heavy like I feel like I had to be positive in that mindset so people
wouldn't come so kind of like they wouldn't bring it to you yeah bring it to me or just feel like
that they're constricted in being because they don't know how it's gonna make me feel because
they know I don't know what it's like to lose somebody like that but I feel like if I did
I would be crazy you know everybody think the extreme that's the impersonation I will be crazy
I'm crazy